Using Free CV Search you have access to featured

directly using the email

misuse of candidate

withheld

option provided. To prevent

information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been

candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice

Important







Associate Architect seeking roles in Project Management

 $, Software\ Development, Requirement\ Gathering, Configuration\ Management, Solution\ Optimization, Risk\ Management, Software\ de-bugging, Software\ Application, Service$

Delivery, Kubernetes, Selenium

Current Designation: Associate Architect

Current Company: Calsoft Pvt. Ltd

Current Location: Pune

Pref. Location: Ahmedabad, Mumbai, Pune

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Team Lead/Tech Lead

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Associate Architect, Team Lead/Tech Lead, Project Management, Software Development, Requirement Gathering, Configuration Management, Solution Optimization, Risk Management, Software de-bugging, Software

Total Experience: 13 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Notice Period: 2 Months
Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [IT]

Application, Service Delivery, Kubernetes, Selenium

Verified : Email - id

Last Active: Jan-Mar 2021

Last Modified: Jan-Mar 2021

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Accomplished Professional with nearly 13 years of extensive experience in Software Development Lifecycle

Rich experience in designing systems/ procedures for change in project operations to design technical solutions, ensuring business functionality adherence and enhancing competitive advantage

Experience in analysis practice with proven capabilities in capturing as-is process, preparing functional specifications & business blueprint document, analysing the gaps

Developed software solutions by studying needs, conferring with users, studying systems flow, data usage and work processes

Proficient in Software Development Life Cycle from requirement analysis to system study, designing, coding, development, de-bugging, documentation and implementation

Followed project life cycle methodology defined under the process framework; ensured that customer deadlines were met within project budgets

Work Experience

- Calsoft Pvt. Ltd as Associate Architect Apr 2015 to Till Date
- Mindtree as Senior Engineer Mar 2012 to Apr 2015
- Exfo as Quality Analyst Jun 2011 to Mar 2012

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (IT) from RGPV, Bhopal in 2007

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name Version Last Used Experience devops

firtualization (VMWARE)
DpenStack DpenStack
Kubernetes, Docker
Ansible
Selenium, Automation
AWS
ELK, API Development
vicro service development
Pytest, Jmeter
Locust
lenkins and Pyvmomi
Python, Powershell
Perl and shell

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
english				
hindi				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Category: **General**Physically Challenged: **No**

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

Work Authorization

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.